(Bernadette:)The next person kicking you
will be me.
(Bernadette:)Good night.
(Howard:)Are we even
in a good school...?
(Howard:)Ow!
(Bernadette:)I warned you,
and I did it.
(Penny:)What's all this?
(Leonard:)Oh, everything we need
for your autograph session--
(Leonard:)head shots, markers.
Okay.
(Penny:)Leonard, it's sweet
you're excited about this,
(Penny:)but it'll be a miracle if one
person asks for my autograph.
(Leonard:)Are you kidding?
I once paid $20
for Theo Sassler's signature.
- Who's that?
- Oh, I don't even know.
(Leonard:)I just liked his name.
Theo Sassler!
Oh, and look at this.
(Leonard:)I even got a change maker.
(Leonard:)How much change you want,
little lady?
(Penny:)Oh, there's so much
I want to change.
(Leonard:)Yeah, well, if it's a dollar,
you're in luck.